

Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City, VietName

□ (+84) 868374742 | Image: Invtanh.dev@gmail.com | Image: Inttps://github.com/nvtanhh | Image: Inttps://www.linkedin.com/in/nvtanh

Summary

Currently working at a France outsourcing company. Mobile Developer with over 2 years of experience in designing, developing, and maintaining mobile applications. I have strong enthusiasm for mobile development and aim to become a full-stack mobile developer. Passionate about bringing ideas to life, thinking out a better problem-solving for challenging tasks, and willing to learn new technologies.

Skills

Programing Dart · NodeJs · Flutter · Docker · Firebase · Hasura (GraphQL) · MySQL · MongoDB

Tool Git · Trello · Redmine · Figma · Adobe XD · ClickUp **Other** UI/UX designing · Presentation · English communication

Work Experience _____

FAVIE TECH. HCMC, Vietnam

MOBILE DEVELOPER · (FLUTTER)

April. 2022 - Present

- Worked in an Agile environment and experienced using ClickUp a project management tool
- · Ability to work on multiple projects and deliver them on time
- Directly work with stakeholders to clarify requirements and raise ideas
- Experienced working with crypto applications
- Experienced working with advanced animation
- Experienced working with AWS Cognito

Dolphin Solutions JSC.

HCMC, Vietnam

Dec. 2020 - March. 2022

MOBILE DEVELOPER \cdot (Flutter)

- Android: https://bit.ly/3FsGVyj | iOS: https://apple.co/33iHddR
- Develop Okuro app (a social network app specialized for education)
- Implemented features: News Feed, Create post, Comment, Search, Chat,... Migrating app to Flutter 2.0
- Working closely with colleagues to develop, maintain app functionality
- Participate in the functional analysis/UI design of some features in the system
- Responsible for release testing/production versions on both Android and iOS
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Familiarity working with widgets, basic animation, Provider, Stream, Bloc, Socket.} io, Storage, \dots in Flutter$

Personal Projects

SOCIAL NETWORK FOR PET · WOOFIE

Dissertation

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER · UI/UX DESIGNER

Feb. 2021 - Aug. 2021

- Android: https://bit.ly/3JcfSLf (not maintained) Demo: https://bit.ly/3I9x1Uh
- Description: Woofie is a specialized social network app for pet and pet lovers
- Team size: 2
- Features:
 - Social network basic features: news feed, create a new post, push notification, comment (real-time), explore, chat (attach: image, video, post),...
 - Manage pet profile with health recordation and reminder
 - Support finding your pets a new family or adopting them
 - Tinder for pet help they find a partner
 - SOS alert "Lost Mode" an extremely useful feature to find a losing pet
- Tech stack:
 - Client: (App & Web) Flutter, GetX, TDD Clean Architecture
 - Social Network Service: GraphQL (Hasura), Go, Postgres
 - Chat Service: Node.Js, Express, MongoDB, Socket.IO
 - 3rd Party services: Firebase Authentication, MinIO (object storage server), One Signal
 - Deployment: Docker, Docker-Compose, Linux

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER · UI/UX DESIGNER

Aug. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- Android: https://bit.ly/3fE4gCN
- Description: This application is a tool to help Vietnamese rappers easy to find rhymes based on a given word and help them write and manage songs, records song
- · Features:
 - Authentication with Facebook and Google
 - Find rhymes based on given word Favorite rhythms list
 - Find the meaning of the word (crawling live data from another dictionary website
 - Song management, record and play song demo
- · Tech stack:
 - Flutter
 - Back-end: Python/ Flask (for find rhymes API); Firebase (for authentication, songs management)
 - Deployment: Heroku

Education

Nong Lam University

HCMC, Vietnam

Bachelor of Information Technology Sep. 2017 - Sep. 2021

- GPA: 3.4/4.0
- Agriculture and Forest University Student of the Year for 3 consecutive years

Honors & Awards _____

HONORS

Oct. 2021	Nong Lam University Student of the Year (2020-2021)
Oct. 2020	Nong Lam University Student of the Year (2019-2020)
Nov. 2020	KMS Grants Scholarships for information technology students at HCMC
Oct. 2019	Nong Lam University Student of the Year (2018-2019)

AWARDS

Nov. 2020 First Prize, 3rd Scientific Research Ideas

Nong Lam University

Extracurricular Activity

Greentea Club (An academic club at the Faculty of Information Technology)

Nong Lam University

EADER

Feb. 2019 - Oct. 2021

- Support the faculty to organize academic and surgical activities
- · Organize programming classes for members and students in the faculty to help them improve their programming skills
- Organize useful programs for Nong Lam University students such as: "Free Windows installation", "Laptop Buying Guide"

July 22, 2022 Tanh Nguyen · Résumé